(Penny:)-Hey, Sheldon.
-Oh, Penny, excellent.
(Sheldon:)I have a question
about these maxi pads.
(Sheldon:)Are the wings truly functional
or have I fallen victim to marketing hype?
(Penny:)What? What are you
doing with--? What?
(Sheldon:)The stock boy at Walgreens was
frustratingly uninformed on the subject.
(Penny:)Sheldon, what are you doing
with maxi pads?
SHELDON: I have a lady friend who will
be staying with me for a few days.
PENNY:
Oh.
(Raj:)What?
SHELDON:
I want her to feel at home.
(Sheldon:)I also bought scented soaps,
pantyhose, Midol, calcium chews...
(Sheldon:)...and what is apparently a yogurt
specifically designed...
(Sheldon:)...to regulate the female bowel.
(Penny:)Wait. Wait, hold on. Back up.
(Penny:)You're having a woman stay with you?
(Sheldon:)Yes. Why does that seem
to flabbergast everybody?
PENNY:
No, no, no, I'm not flabbergasted.
(Penny:)I'm puzzled.
(Penny:)Yeah, let's go with puzzled.